It turned, you know, John Pierre.
I do, umm, I'm
coming across from TD
Callum. Originally Cowen rebranded
kind of as TD
Cowan after the acquisition
and I had had
the pleasure of having
John as my dedicated
resource. Well, the cow on earth
D Nice. Yeah, he's good. He's
great. I must have worked with
him for over a year and
a half. Probably to get where
we need it to be and
everything. Yep. Fantastic. Fantastic
guy. Good. Good.
You can tell him he owes me a beer.
He'll say sure, where you at
exactly?
Who are we waiting for?
OK. Next
week. And
Anya or Daniel or do we want
to begin? Do we need to wait
for other folks? We're almost to the
five minute mark. No, I think we
can. We can proceed. Yeah. OK. Well,
I'm going to start off first by
asking is there any questions? So last
meeting. Um, we did like
a kick off and we explained how
to use e-mail fraud defense. Have you
come up with any questions since then
that you would like to have answered?
So I've got one question. So I've been
poking around in it just a bit as
of yesterday and in the reports. Is there
a way for us to?
To generate like I
think. But we'll be
adding for example, is say for example
t.com. And so ideally I want to
see everything sub domain wiseundertd.com
specifically. So can we create a group
for that and then report to show
the coverage like the percentage of
emails that are passing detail like looks
like that's. Possible, but that is a
typical report. That is a typical report.
OK, let me share my Well, would you
rather share your screen or do you want
me to share mine? Do you have a
preference? I'll let you drive. OK, let
me show you.
Let me know when you're able to
see my screen. You should see e-mail
fraud defense. OK, that's it. So you
kind of stay to what you already
needed to do. I mean, you go
into create report, but if you want
it for td.com and sub domains, then
there's a little trick. That you'd want
to do so um let's just
chat yeah I didn't think I
saw any there so you click
on create group and it needs
to be a dynamic group you
click next and here if you're
after everything you really don't want
to. Specify sending or non sending and
then again here you wouldn't have to
specify anything here. But the trick is
this here you want to type in
the name of the apex domain right?
So you select it, but in order to see
all the subdomains you got to check this
thing right here. And then of course you
got to give it a name. And I don't
know if this is what you want, but we
can do. I
guess td.com and
subdomains. I don't know if that's the
name you want, but.
So now I got my group and then
it's just a matter of of, uh, positioning
the widgets. So my interest, what am I
interested in most? Maybe at the top you
can drag these around a lot like the
canvas, So you can. You can drag
them around, um, but it's the wedges
that you may want to look at.
So you have multiple widgets. Domain
policy. Domain policy is useful if you're
starting a demark journey and you have
X number of domains and and you
just want to track it. Over a
period of time to see them go
from maybe no record, maybe to none,
and then to your reject or quarantine
policy. It would be an example. So
domain policy would be helpful in that.
Here, let me just say I'm just
going to save them all. You do
have tables. So everybody's a little bit
different. Some people are fine with the
charge that we provide. Some people
really like the data table. Everybody,
you know, is different. I'm just going to
save the defaults for right now so you
can see them. So once I have my
report created, you'll see it listed down
below. And when you when
you click on that, you'll come
to the tab and you'll have
the top. Unless you change things
around the default, it's going to
have Demark progress 1st. And Demark
progress is based upon permitted senders.
So if you remember firmware. Conversation
in the previous meeting we talked about
creating the canvas, you know using the
different tools there to mark a senders
permitted or not permitted.
So this is where you can come
to kind of get an idea. Well,
how well are our permitted emails passing
Dr. And it should be high, right?
The only time it may not be
is if you look down here, follow
my mouse this purple. Purple is
something you want to watch for. Um,
I would maybe recommend to look at
the reports once a month. Not a
daily thing, but you know, schedule it
to look at it once a month.
And, and the reason why is sometimes
not very often, but I've seen instances
where. A provider, um
or excuse me, a
vendor makes a change
in their DNS with
unintended consequences and it
can affect delivery.
So again, I don't see it very often, but
it is possible. But what what you'd end
up seeing if they did that is typically
you're going to have purple kind of
overlay this green line if you fall on my
mouse. I, I just
want to, uh, not, I guess dive off
into some direction here. I just wanted
to, so we can create a report we
can show just specifically td.com and all
of its subdomains. Yeah, perfect. Is that
something that is once we've created, is
that seen by everyone who has access to
this?Do we have to create that report
per user? It's a per user thing. So
if they wanted to, yeah. So how do
we make reports that are available for
the group? We don't have that capability.
If you come up here to the megaphone
and go to product documentation or,
excuse me, I clicked on the wrong thing,
my bad. Product feedback. This is
where you come to to submit an
enhancement. So I would submit it. I've
had a few customers ask about it, but
not many really not many requested to be
honest. But if that's important for you,
then I would submit it and then product
management will do what they do. You
know, in order to prioritize what they
add and the product next. So but that's
yeah, that's, that's a pretty important
thing because we don't want to onboard a
new user and have to walk them through
creating all the reports that we've
established as critical for monitoring.
Yeah. So right now to be the stakeholder.
Who has access can set it up
and then they would have to get
screenshots and share it, unfortunately.
All right. So separately like once the
report we have something on the screen
and we show where, where failure is
occurring. Is there any dive into that
data? Like could we see further detail?
Uh, if we have an anomaly
here, yeah, so.
What I would do is the canvas
is really good to see like high
level things. But in this case, right
here, let's say that we had some
purple on a specific time frame, right?
Then you can go into IP viewer.
If you remember, we talked about the
search tools. So if you
go to the search tool, particularly the
IP viewer, then you can specify the
date range. So it would need. So
if that's the situation where you're
seeing some purple for permitted emails,
then I would make a note of
the time and then go to IP.
Year make the time match and then the
other thing that you can do is there's a
current sender here. Let me just ensure
that the the data that we see in that
report is not something we can dig into.
We have to like take a note of where
that is that we're interested in finding
information and even looking at that if
we're looking at. Like as as like a
group, right? TDL subdomains, that data
doesn't say what it's specifically
related to it some part within that data
set, it doesn't identify what it is,
right? So, yeah, right. So you just
basically would be going to IP viewer and
using the same criteria that you have for
your report. Date range and then we'll
what am I? Which of these charts?
Ohh, I'm looking for not permitted,
undetermined. And then over here in IP
viewer you could say something like
current sender and you can say, well,
I'm looking at permitted or I'm looking
for undetermined or not permitted date
range. And the idea is you want to
make the IP viewer, you want to give it
the same data as the chart you're looking
at here. So if we're looking at Demark
block, right, and you're trying to figure
out, well, wait a second, I would expect
to see a whole lot more mail being
blocked than what I see here. It's only
17%. Well, there's reason for that. We
already talked about the RUAUM. We may
not be getting that. And by the
way, last week when we had talked
about the Rua.
You can have three.
Male choose for an RUA&RUF.
However, what we've found is
that some destinations will only
report on the 1st 2,
not the third.
Yeah, we're, so we're gonna be using
three. We'll be using two at most. OK,
anyway, but the idea is, is to use
this right here and then go to IP
viewer to get more granular view about
this. For example on the 27th, you know,
why are we seeing in so much purple?
And we would expect to see this, but
again, the argula would contribute to
that. If we're not, if we're not getting
the full visibility, we're we're not
going to show you the full picture,
right? And so that could be it.
Or it actually could be a sender. And
I don't think you guys have done this
yet with your canvas, so I don't think
this would be the situation, but it's a
possibility. When you're permitting
senders, sometimes you might mark a
sender as at that time as not permitted,
but in the future someone could switch
where they say. But we're not using
Sendgrid, we're going to switch to
Mailgun. Well, Mel
gun at that at the previous time
would have been marked as not permitted.
And so now if if they went
through and they've authorized and
everything, you'd have to go into the
not permitted in the canvas, mark it
as permitted and then Sendgrid since.
Some longer permit it would need to be
marked as not permitted and then after it
kind of depends on the date range, but
probably safe to say within 30 days you'd
have a better report of what you would
expect based upon the change and and and
final questions. So are there any reports
that?Would be generated in e-mail or or
do we have to visit the the portal
here? You have to visit the portal. There
is a report. So you have APIs, we
haven't talked about it yet, but you can
pull data via API. Yeah, understood. And
so we don't need to go into that
but. Is, is there any monitoring?
I'm kind of bouncing around a little bit,
so I apologize, but it is good. So some
of the emails that we get today is we get
notices.
Is where an SPF record is created is
changed or Decam records changed? Is Is
this also capable of monitoring those and
and alerting on those changes for DMARC
and SPF? Yes. You would set it up
for these two alerts right? Demark record
and if you click on these it says
3 but you got 3.
Three items you can choose
Demark record change, multiple or
inconsistent and then Demark errors
or warnings. Same for SPF.
Yep. So you just subscribe,
you know, and then you'll
start receiving those reports.
If you need to.
You can also pause it. So let's say you
say, well, I understand what the issue
is. We're we're fixing it, but I don't
want the alert. So what you could do is
come here, you could see I've got it
disabled. But what I can do is I can
pause that alert for a period of time.
Now I haven't, I haven't got it set up
so. But but it can be paused
if I need it to be. So,
OK. But yeah, just alerted the dashboard
itself, right? Yes, Sir. Yeah. OK. And
these again are going to be user
specific. So if you set up the
you subscribe to an alert, you're just
subscribing yourself. Right. So
understood. OK, Alright, thank you. Thank
you. Yeah. Yeah. Well, happy to answer
any questions.
So what we didn't
cover in the previous
meeting is supplier Risk
Explorer. Look alike domains
and hosted services along with well, we
didn't cover reports either, but we kind
of did that right now, so I'm
not worried about that.
Look alike domains.
Is away and I can't show you because I
don't think we got to see. No, we don't.
Look, Alikes, so Demark does a
great job of protecting yourorganization.
From bad actors that
are using that specific
spelling or characters for
your domain.
But it doesn't protect you from look
alikes, you know we're a bad actor
could could take. I don't know if
TD's a good example, but if you
had another domain that had multiple
characters, they might be able to
substitute an A or an ID or.
Various different characters. They could
substitute it for some international
character as an attempt to
get someone to bite on
a fish massage. You know,
BC whatever campaign they're trying
to launch.
He mark doesn't protect you against that,
so that's why we added the look
alike domains feature. If you want to
use it, then you go to system
under system down here and to the
right is where you come to configure
it. Now it's going to say there's
no act of seeds. The way this
tool works is we look at the
apex domains. So if I say confirm
seed, it's going to bring me in
here step 1-2 and three. But first
step is adding the seeds and this
is where you'd want to add in
the look alikesnowtd.com. It's going to
be tough, guys. There's 2 characters. You
can have so many variations of that.
They would do or what they would
recommend is is. Maybe it might be
better to use um.
TD Bank. You know,
you, you, you kind of have to think like
a bad actor. So if I was going to
create a look alike, you know.
How how would I do that?
You know, TD is is might
be too short because of all
the variations for you to protect
against or monitor for. Well, we
do not maybe in lots of
other variations today. What what does
what does TD?It's an
abbreviation, right? What does T? It is,
It's around the menu.
So that might be something you could use,
but you want to think this out. Just
don't put in a 2 character or three
character. You kind of want to think,
well what are the bad guys going to do?
And I'm sure your security team has
already seen instances. So that would be
a good place to go to or resource to
go to say. These security, we have this
feature look alikes, you know what have
you seen in the past because we need
to add a seed that's going to catch
the look alikes that we're interested in.
Maybe not those that we don't care
about. South detection is key, that's
all. Yeah, like I said, we do
this today. We do monitor for the
keyword TD, unfortunately, because it
gets split with hyphens, underscores, all
variations that you can think of, you
know, and and and. Keyboard typos and
so any, any domain registrar with TD in
it, unfortunately, I have to look at it.
Do you have, are you saying that you
have another service you're using that
does the same thing? OK, so it's up
to you. It's part of the service. You
know, it's not any extra money.
But if you wanted to configure it and
test it out, I would recommend to add,
you know, two or three seeds and then
you can go look, We'd probably use this
in some capacity probably from a threat
defense operations perspective. But the,
the reason for the other service is for
for, for legal enforcement. OK.
So, and we said, let's see one
one thing to call out, sorry to
interrupt. I'm included in your license
is a takedown service. So you can
submit takedowns from our portal. You
might want to use your legal service,
but also use us in conjunction because
we can also do like soft takedowns.
Where we can, which are much faster, we
can go to our URL lists, our own
service and make the take that down as
you work through a hard takedown. We also
have relationships with the registrars,
so it's something that you can make use
of. You could submit the takedown request
from here or. From the takedown portal,
yeah, for sure. We'll definitely take a
look at it and evaluate its capabilities
and see where it fits in our process. But
the majority of the use cases that I'm
chasing down our trademark based. So. So
that's why it has to go through a legal
process. We have to have letters we have
to have. Follow up letter etcetera until
it's remediated. But for for threats that
are detected, we'll, we'll certainly
consider this for for takedowns. OK, just
one other thing before I forget, don't
I don't know why, but I've seen
a lot of Caspers just start adding
ignore rules without looking at the.
Protections. Please add your seeds,
get the detections. If you're
going to use the service,
add your seeds, look or
evaluate the detections, then come
back and create Ignore rules
because if you do it
too early, you're actually going
to. Prevent seeing some look alikes
that you need to block or you
need to take action on. So keep
that in mind. And the other gotcha
is this corporate name servers.
Corporate name servers, if you add them
here, only add a name server you
have control over. For example, if you're
using Akamai, I think you've got the
name right. If you use an Akamai
or GoDaddy or something like that, you
wouldn't want to add those name servers
here. Why? Because they those nameservers
are serving other organizations. And so
by adding them here again, you're going
to prevent some detections from being
seen. And then you might be on
the phone with me saying to him,
you know, we're we were expecting to
see this look alike. We found it
here, but we don't see it here why And
it's either going to be related to the
ignore rules you created or it's going to
be related to the corporate name servers.
So just a word of caution, if you are
going to use the service, I would, I
would encourage you to use it, but it's
up to you. Um, look alike
alerts is here. So if you need
to add an alert, you do it
here. Um, there's multiple conditions you
can use. You can and or you
can, you know, use ORS and Ands
or complex conditions.
And these are the ones you can choose
from. And you can, if
you're using the tag results, you can
use that as well, so.
Logos. I didn't. I skipped that part. My
back. Let me go back over here.
Hundreds of corporate name servers you
also have logos so the the
service is capable of scanning when
we're going out crawling the Internet
looking for look alikes we'll we'll
look for the logos that you've
added here very helpful so.
That's really look alike domains. Um,
I can't really demo the detections
because you got to add a
seed first. You can only add
a seed if it's claimed and
you've proven ownership. If you've done
that, you can add.
An apex domain as AC,
no role based access control.
Presently they're targeting I think
it's the third or fourth
quarter of this year. So,
but role based access control
is coming, we just can't
say exactly when but. With look
alike domains it's increased the the
priority of making sure that we get
that added. But they've been working on
role based access control for a few
years because it involves multiple
products. So it's not something they can
just knock out, you know, because it's
involving multiple products, so. That's
look alike. Umm, we can talk more if you
were to add some seeds. If you have
questions about the detections, then you
just need to reach out to me and and
if we have a regularly scheduled meeting,
we can talk about it then. Or if you
just want to do an ad hoc, we can
do that. Whatever you need.
Um.
I'm going to skip Supplier Risk Explorer
right now. I'm going to come up and talk
more about hosted services.
So.
Hosted SPF. So we've got all
these services here. Bimmy is fairly
new. I want to say maybe
about four months. I might have
that wrong, but hosted services is
very helpful if you're on the
journey. Now realize you got many
domains that reject or quarantine.
But there there is benefits and they're
going to be the same as what Agari
or anybody else provides that are they're
using dynamic SPF is I think what some
call it, but. But
there are certain benefits #1 if you
have a high volume domain, you may
have many vendors that you're using, and
you may have heard about the DNS
query limit. Well, that's the reason why
you might want to use hosted SPF
is to get around that.
It's very easy to set up. First thing
you do is you have to enroll and
that you would do for hosted Decam,
hosted Mark, hosted Bimmy first step is
to enroll the domains. Enrolling's real
easy. You just come here and either paste
in a list or you do a search.
And then um. And
then once they've been enrolled,
then you need to manage
them. So, um, you click
on it and it's going
to bring you into this
Screener. Right here 5
you can see what needs to be
replaced if you're going to have this,
um. Handle
request. Coming in for
SPF for this domain, if you're going to
have us handled for all the senders, then
you would use this. If you're going to
go for a hybrid, then you would use
this. So you'll notice that the include
is really the same for both.
What you have to do to set up
a hybrid is we would prefer that you
have us at the first position. For
example, when I say position you have V
equals SPF one. Well then you may have
some other include. Well it's at the
first position, you would want to put a
macro in front of it.
Why telemetry? So some of
you that's been maybe working
with e-mail for a long
time. You would know
that a lot of times SPF records
really are never cleaned up, which means
that they're overly permissive. So if I
had a sender and I moved away
from that sender and I left them
in there, basically I'm giving.
Someone permission who could use that
sender to send out so it's
recommended to clean it up with
telemetry. It makes it possible.
Telemetry will not be available until
it goes live. What is and
to go live. What you're going
to do is as an example.
This is the current SPF record. Once
you've gone through managing the senders
to go live, you're going to swap
this with this if you want us
to manage all of the senders. And
again, if you wanted to hybrid, then
you would want to put this right
after this. And then put um and
include to the right or in Max. Whatever
the mechanism is, you would put it to
the right if you needed a hybrid.
When, when you, when you unroll it, we're
going to, we pull in the SPF record
immediately. So you'll see this. And if
there's any nested includes, you can, you
know, expand them to see them.
Managed Sanders is where you come to
configure it though. So before you go
live, you need to configure it. And So
what we're going to do is we're going
to pull in those includes here. So we're
going to pull them in here. It won't
be active. It will show, no.
Then you could choose to say, hey, I
want I want proof point to manage all
of these senators. You just select that
you say add to hosted record and then
all of this right here is going to
switch to a yes. And assuming there's no
other senders that you need to add.
Then you can publish or
make the switch from the
SPF record to the macro,
and then once it propagates
this will switch to being
live. Then we're in your
mail flow, so we'll be
answering any SPF request. On your
behalf as they come in.
Um.
Documentation for hosted SPF If you
come up here to the megaphone,
we have both videos and we
have product documentation. The videos
are not very long. We keep
them short to the point because
we know that administrators are busy
so but. This is where they
are. So this is a good
place of of it's just a
good resource. And then product
documentation is another place. And
again, here's the information for hosted
SPF, hosted DTM, hosted DeMar.
So this is where you become um.
To learn more about it.
If I come back over here to manage
senders.
When you click on add senders, I'm going
to describe this as a basic find.
Sometimes you'll put in a sender name and
you won't get any result. Or you may
put in an include and you don't get
a result or an IP sider. Don't sweat
it, just come up here to advance. Specify
that mechanism. I'll just choose include
and then you put in the domain and submit
it. That will add it to the list and it
will be yes. The
caveat to this tool is if you take one
of these to a yes, then we're going to
start filtering this column. This will
show as blue and you're only going to see
the ones that have it yes. So you want
to make sure you check that select all so
you can see everything.
Any questions about hosted
SPF?
The 90 day date range or the date range
is where you can specify it um.
So that way if you are checking
telemetry, um, you can specify the date
range, for example, Most people are not
going to remove someone unless it's 90
days or older. They want that period
of time to pass before they feel
comfortable that yeah, this really isn't
being. Used or what a lot
of customers will do is they'll
say well I can see the
observed queries is really low you
know one in the last 90
days well does that mean we're
moving away from that sender So
typically an organization is going. When
they add a service here, they may use
service now, they may use remedy. But
through those means you could find out,
well, who do I need to talk to
about this sender to find out if we're
still using them because the telemetry is
kind of is indicating to me that it's
not being. So I just
don't want to Willy nilly remove it. I
want to at least verify with someone my
to know if they if we really did
move away from them or not. Maybe they're
a very random sender or seasonal.
Any questions about hosted SPF?
One of the things I didn't talk about is
templates. Templates
can save an administrator time.
Um, for example, let's say
that I had 10 domains
and the SPF record is
the same for all of
them. They use the exact
same senders. Well, instead
of enrolling all of those, what I
could do is I could come in
the template to create a template.
Pull in those and roll those
domains, and then what it can
do from there is manage the
senders, and instead of having to
do it 10 separate times, I
just did it once. That's only
useful if they're identical.
You can't have a hybrid with templates
right now.
We're, you know, we're maybe one of
the 10 has an additional sender, but
everything else is the same. You can't
do a hybrid yet, so.
That would be it for hosted SPF, but I
would encourage you to look at the
documentation. And
videos.
Poster Dekim.
Um, for the most part it's very
similar to hosted SPF. The only
difference is is when you enroll a
domain, it's going to have you specify
whether it's non delegated or delegated.
You're always going to want to choose
delegated you. You really don't want to
use non. Non delegated.
The reason is due to
C names, so you can
add some C names here,
but non delegated a little
bit wonky as far as
you could use it, but
you're adding it to your
own DNS. 1st and you're kind
of putting the scene name over to
the sender. It's wonky. I wouldn't really
recommend to ever choose non delegated
delegate is just simpler. It's more
straightforward.
Once you have it enrolled, then the
next step would be very similar to
hosted SPF, but in this case you're
going to be adding selectors. When you
add a selector, we have multiple options
to choose from. You can import detected
selectors. This is where we are just
going to. Um, list any that
we found. Or
you could import the selectors by name,
so this is where you would give the
name or provide the name for each of
the selectors. So that's how
you could quickly start using our service
for a given domain. I'm partial to import
selectors by name. Why? Because I can I
can get a dump of the zone file
for that domain and then I just need
to find those lines that have the
selector. So it's either going to be a
tax record. Seen it and so once
I have the selector names I know
I'm not missing anything. This is hit
and miss. Yes I could import in
what it found, but I don't know
what it didn't find. So I'm going
to the zone file anyway to determine
what will what selectors do we have.
So it's up to you, but you could use this
to do part of the labor. You could use
this to finish up the labor, or you could
use this because you're going to be
looking at the zone file anyway. Totally
up to you.
Once you have all of these imported
in the remaining two options this this
will change once you start adding
selectors or once it goes live. Excuse
me, once it goes live you only
have direct TXT, racker, or CA.
So if I were to choose direct TXT
record, you know, you give it the
selector name and then you give it the
public key because this is a tax record.
And then I would recommend that you
specify well, who is the sender.
And then we add this in here
automatically for you. If it's checked
you can uncheck it, but the default
is Leave it checked for RSA.
There's ECC that's starting to get used
more and more in the industry, so
if it's ECC, you would not want
to check this.
So you can use DNS SAC, just
make sure your DNS SAC is properly
configured. But you can use DNSSEC and
when you delegate it, we're all you're
only delegating the_domain key. I don't
know if you noticed that. 4
but you're delegating that sub domain
to proof point. To make this
go live, you would have to
add these two nameservers to name
server records to your DNS. That's
how you get this to go
live. Any
questions with posted decon?
OK.
Bolsa de mark is probably the easiest to
set up. Um, you still enroll the domain,
but it's going to have you start walking
through. Well, what options do you want?
Do you want reject, you know, quarantine
none or do I need to do it?
Asked them if I need to add some tags
that I normally wouldn't use. Umm. And
then if you're next to it, then you
select your domain or you choose the
domains that you're going to use this
for. But in order to make it go live,
this is a little different. You're going
to take the scene name that we provide
you and add it to your DNS. And
then next and then after DNS propagation
it will show live.
Do you guys are you using Bimmy?
In a very limited capacity. OK. Binny's
pretty easy to configure as well. You got
to enroll it. Do you mind if I
enroll like td.com? It's not live or
anything, but it helps me demo it a
little better. Is that OK?
That's just enrolled in terms of your
dashboard, it's not going right. Yes,
it's not live right. OK, give me just
a second here.
OK, so once it's enrolled then you
have to add a selector. So Benny's
similar to DKIM, but you have to
add a selector. A lot of times
the selector is going to be default
and that's fine.
But if you want to go with
the default selector then you just choose
next and then we will add it
in. If you want to go with
a custom selector like a lot of
times if you're using sub domains, it
would have its own logo and.
And so you could choose custom if you
need to. What
I'm going to do is rather than pursue
that, I'm going to come over to my portal
real quick.
So within my portal right here.
I have this zizzer.net, if I
select that to come into it
then when I add the selectors
let me just edit this one.
Sorry.
Then I can upload the upload
the logo. Or
I can specify if you've already
like um. That loaded up
someplace. You can specify here and we
can go find it. It's just an HTTP://PATH.
And then if it's a verified mark
certificate, you can choose that. Mine's
not so I'm not going to choose that,
but very easy to set up for Bimmy.
If you want us to handle that, you
know the quarters for that then or the
validation for that and we can do that
so. That covers
it for the hosted services.
You're quiet group, no questions.
OK, um.
What you're talking about records?
The supplier risk explorer
is um.
This is very handy.
So if you're using tap within
pod, so if you have the
inbound traffic going through a pod,
then this will give you visibility
to senders that could pose a
risk to your organization. So this
isn't so much about Demark.
As it is, um, well, let me
switch over to yours again. Just give
me just a second because I don't
have any traffic.
We don't see anything for you guys
either. There's no
traffic here.
Um, yeah. So if I'm not
seeing any traffic, it doesn't sound
like your MX records is pointing
to POD.
Uh, not for this instance. Umm, I think
that this is the production instance
We're doing all the testing and all the
stuffing that ohh, OK in the type
instance, right. So that's why you're not
going to see anything in the under the TD
Bank financial. That's OK, I can demo
this later, but basically supply risk
explorer is really meant to. To give
you visibility, it's just a monitoring
tool, no different DFD.
But it gives you visibility
to domains that pose a
risk to your recipients.
And it it leverages
what tap gives you.
Um, but this tool will
eventually be going away. It's
going to be replaced by
supplier. Threat
Protection STP. So I
don't know if you
guys purchased that or
not, but. But
this is really good as far as at
a high level getting the idea well who
could be who is sending to our
recipients, who could be a risk because
what we would show over at the right
here, let me try and do this. This
is not really all that sensitive with
data. Um, let's
see.
There we go. We'll just sit here. Think
we got beta here?
There we go. So you
have all domains and suppliers.
Suppliers, What's going to is the default
and that's what's going to show you
down below. This is based on the
header from. But the idea is as
we see inbound mail, we're looking, we
use a.
A language learning model that base is
looking at the inbound traffic to see
if there's any type of financial type
of information. If we see it like
in last seven days, depending on what
we have here, we're going to show
it as high risk if you're past
seven days. The risk will lower to
be in kid appears very high risk
and then it could show as as
high risk over a period of time.
But you can see when I click
on intuit.com. They're
cashmere, we talked about this, but,
um. You'll get
this pop up. You'll have these three
tabs, general domains, look alikes. So it
will remind you what the risk is. It
will show you the company for that domain
registration date, all this good
information. You can see if there's other
sub domains that they're sending from and
if there's any look alikes. To show
it here, but what makes this
useful is you can look at
this and go OK, three fishing
messages last seven days. Seven of
them were bec well, if you're
using tap. If you're
tap administrator then this should be
clickable or drillable, meaning if I
click on it.
It's going to show me the
three fishing messages that came inbound
to my to your plot.
And over here at the far right, you can
click this and it will take you into the
dashboard, the tap dashboard. Now, I'm
not a tap dashboard, so I'm not going to
take you in there because I can show you
the obvious things. But people on this
phone are going to know more about me if
they're in tap every day. So I would
recommend that if you're interested in
this, you know, and you have
availability, I would come in to look at
it.
And a lot of times most CFD consultants
are not going to be able. This will
not work for us to be honest, unless
they've requested the TAP access.
Now we have to spread down below.
The spread is just to give you
an idea of of well, you know
in the proof point community how many
are seeing phishing, BEC and malware
that's related to here.
So it's a good way to kind of determine.
Who could? Who are our suppliers
that we care about? If they
are a supplier, you can check
this and click on Add suppliers.
Now instead of showing discovered, they
will show as a supplier. So
I've always recommended you know.
Look for minimally the top ten, identify
top ten and then understand well what
risk are they posing to my users.
And if you are a tap expert
and you see fish or you see
malware, then I would drill into that.
Typically pods going to catch it.
I've yet to see an instance where
Pod didn't catch it, but.
What I would worry about if I was
administrator is, well, great, pod did
his job, I'm glad. But if they're sending
up fishing, I wonder if they know that
they have a problem. So if it's a
partner, you're going to have someone you
might be able to reach out to and
you can give them. Samples to say look,
are you aware that you're sending this?
We would really like you to do
something about it. So if you know
about it, wonderful. You know, if they're
acting on it, wonderful, but they may
not know about it. So, so it's,
it's a, it's a handy tool to
see who is who could be.
Problem for you and your users.
Any questions about supplier risk
explore just just so is
this the only place for
this information is located? It
is. Would this be somewhere
in TAP as well? Well,
that's where supplier threat. Protection
STP comes in. STP is an add-on
for town now. Navindra could talk to
you more about it. He probably knows
more about SDP than I do. So
if if you're interested just to know
what it does you know, I would
work with lavender or and AND.
Set up a time, have someone
just explain it. I'm not the
salesman, OK? I'm not here to
sell you, but this gives you
really good information. STP since it's
part of is going to give
you better information. But the thing
about the gateway. Is it has teeth
where you can do something about it? This
does not have any teeth. Yes, can
illustrate it. So yeah, I'm just trying
it for context with the threat defense
team need access to this so that they
could perhaps have visibility of this
information. Yeah, you'd have to go up.
Then go to access management and give
them access to your ID. But yeah,
OK, alright, yeah, thank you. Now I
have a lot of customers that take
this route and it's totally up to
you, but I have a lot of
customers that say, hey Tim, where's the
API's for this?We're going to pull
this into Splunk where we can do what
we want to do and we can set
up maybe some alerts to have someone
check on it. So if if you're interested
in that, then again, it's under the APIs.
Don't know if we have time to really talk
about it today, but what I'm going to do
is I'm going to put in the link to
our API documentation for EFD.
Let me grab this link, I'm going to paste
it in there and then if you guys have
follow up questions. Specific to
the API and what it can give you, I
can help you with that. I cannot help you
if you're using a third party like Swan
to do something with the data. That's
where your people need to be skilled
enough to know. But I'm going to put this
into the chat. You can copy it out,
bookmark it.
OK, so we've got 4 minutes left. I've
demoed everything how to use the tool. If
you have any follow up questions, just
reach out to me either individually or if
you have enough people that have enough
questions maybe we can do an ad hoc
meeting, whatever you want. Um.
So the question becomes, what do we do
next?So we talked about the
Rua needs to be added to give us
visibility. That's going to take a little
bit of time for you. Well, maybe I don't
know, you guys might have a script that
does knocks it out, I don't know, but.
But how can I help you going forward?
I don't think we're going to that in
3 minutes, but we'll develop that. OK.
All right, feel free to send me e-mail.
So if you, if you're saying, hey, Tim,
this is our direction. This is how we
need your help with e-mail fraud defense.
By all means, just reach out. Like I
said, we can do a meeting anytime. So
yeah, in short, I think we just need to
get a domain and testing and understand
what we're seeing or not seeing as
comparison to apples to apples for the
existing product because I don't think
any comparison was ever done or provided
for what was. In use today.
Is that correct?
Thursday. That's
fair to say. Yeah. We never saw it.
It's you guys, you guys. All right. So,
yeah, so that's kind of what needs to
happen. That's why there's some few
questions at the beginning just to
understand where we're at with the
product today with proof point and how it
compares and where the where the gap or.
For the features overlap, Yeah, and I
think we've already I gotta go look, I
thought we gave you a health check and
you have the health check, right?
Did OK, Never mind. Well, that's all
we have. We got about two minutes
left. I can give you something some
time back. Can end on
that, if that.
So yeah, I'm good then. Thank you. Now
the Andrew, did you have anything you
wanted to add? We got like one minute.
Nothing in the one minute, but yeah, you
guys do have license to surprise their
prevention. Um, we'll cover that in one
of. Uh, the deep
dive sessions on um.
On the threat protection implementation,
any but you want to add preview I
can always give you guys a walk through.
And which product was it in the bedroom?
It's it's supply threat prevention, the
integration. Yeah. Yeah, I got it. Yeah.
With the work bench. And that happened we
have correct. No, it is a product that
you own. OK. So it's part of work
work branch Noventa did I hear? Right.
Well, they owned the license. As part
of the impersonation protection package,
which includes SCR. Yeah, I did not.
I didn't know that. So thank you.
OK, thank you. Was trying to say
something. Go ahead on you.
No, I'm good. I just needed to
mute 2 left. Alright, alright, OK,
alright. I think at some point we'll
do that, but first steps on this,
we'll evaluate the comparison and prepare
a plan for it. The other thing
though, before you drop, I just want
to make sure. You you have
Kitty Kalen, which runs on a separate
tenant. What's your intention? Do you
want to keep these accounts? You have the
console separate. You're looking at
merging it. We're going to merge it, OK.
Um, we have a plan on how we're
going to implement that. That's what,
what was it Noel was asking you
previously on how we're going to do it.
And that is just going to stream into
when we cut over the domains to at
least our proof point instance when
we're. Um. Which McCall
it once we're like once we're OK
with setting up our production instance
basically OK, OK, OK, let me know.
We've got a meeting next Wednesday. If
we if you want to meet, great.
If you don't want to meet and
we don't have much to talk about,
I don't really. I don't really have
anything else to talk about unless you
guys give me some direction. All I can do
is say, hey, these are what needs to be
addressed from a demark perspective. I
think I've already done that. So just let
me know what you want to do. OK? Thank
you. You're welcome. Bye. Bye.